

About Me

I am 26 years old enthusiastic, self-motivated, reliable, responsible, hard working and happy person from Lithuania. Almost my whole life I was improving communication skills and team based tasks. I decided to focus all my energy and passion so I'm very willing to learn and develop new skills.

Currently self-educating.



+3706 0403991



ugnius.uscilas@gmail.com



www.linkedin.com/in/ugnius-uscilas

LANGUAGE

- English
- Lithuanian
- Basics Russian

EXPERTISE

- Junior Developer
- Frontend Developer
- Leadership
- Critical Thinking
- Time Management
- REACT
- JavaScript
- NEXT.js
- HTML/CSS

UGNIUS USCILAS

Junior Software Developer

EXPERIENCE

UAB EECO Lithuania 2024

While studying at KITM, I completed a 2-month internship at the company UAB EECO. And worked there for 3 months.

- Collaborated with the team to understand requirements and business specifications.
- Was creating mobile application from scratch.
- Used best practices in React and CSS to develop dynamic mobile application based on existing web application.

Kaunas KITM school Lithuania 2023 - 2024

I graduated from KITM, where I studied to become a Full-Stack Developer, with a focus on Front-End Development. During my studies, I learned various technologies such as Node.js, React, JavaScript, SQL, NoSQL, Git, GitHub, HTML & CSS, and Sass and so on. Additionally, I acquired skills in Linux and the basics of Python. In several group projects, I served as the team leader.

Jonava sport school Lithuania 2004 - 2016

In this period of time I played football which is team sport. During that time I gained amount of experience to communicate with people, work together as a team.

Lithuanian Military Lithuania 2016 - 2023

In all those years I was squad leader and completed couple of courses related to leadership. In military I continued improving communication and leadership skills because I had to train soldiers to work as a team.

EDUCATION

Secondary education

Jonava Senamiestis gymnasium 2012 - 2016

Professional education

Kaunas KITM 2023-2024